<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quantum Federated Learning Blog</title>
    <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Quantum Federated Learning Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review: &#39;&#39;Explainer: What is a Quantum Computer?&#39;&#39;</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post5/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 8, 2021)
On 29 January 2019, the MIT Technology Review published an article1 by Martin Giles on the subject of Quantum Computing. This piece, titled &amp;ldquo;Explainer: What is a Quantum Computer&amp;rdquo; is a short overview of what makes quantum computing unique and how it contributes to the technological world. In particular, this article stands out to me because of its easy-to-comprehend definitions of quantum properties. Here, I outline these properties:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Mathematical Theory Behind TensorFlow Quantum for Hybrid Learning</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post4/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 8, 2021)
The paper &amp;ldquo;TensorFlow Quantum: A Software Framework for Quantum Machine Learning&amp;rdquo; by Michael Broughton, et al. introdues the TensorFlow Quantum library with respect to implementing hybrid models that handle classical or quantum data 1. In this post, I attempt to give a brief explaination of the equations given in Section III, &amp;ldquo;Theory of Hybrid Quantum-Classical Machine Learning.&amp;rdquo;
Equation (1) This equation can be considered the starting point for our Quantum Neural Network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review: &#39;&#39;How to get started in quantum computing&#39;&#39; </title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post3/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 3, 2021)
Summary David Matthews&#39; paper &amp;ldquo;How to get started in quantum computing,&amp;rdquo; by Nature News, is an excellent survey paper of today&amp;rsquo;s state of computing. Published online just a few months ago on 4 March 2021, it summarizes fundamental ideas behind quantum computing motivating new research. The paper names leading companies and institutions who have been contributing to the swiftly growing field, and it distinguishes a few broad aspects of their approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classical versus Quantum Computing</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 3, 2021)
There exist a plethora of methods of computation. The most commonly used computation is classical computation. Here, we explore the basic differences between classical and quantum.
Classical Computing Also known as binary computing, classical computing is a system of computation that uses bits (represented by 0 and 1) to logically store and manipulate information. Historically, all computers from Babbage&amp;rsquo;s theoretical &amp;ldquo;analytical machine&amp;rdquo; to the supercomputers produced by Hewlett Packard Enterprise&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary, Cray Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to My Research</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post1/</guid>
      <description>Federated Deep Learning on Quantum Computers Welcome to my blog about my undergraduage honors computer science research! I am excited to start working this summer in preparation for my senior year at William &amp;amp; Mary.
Brief Summary Many edge devices, such as cell phones, contribute to and require feedback from a shared deep learning algorithm hosted on a server. For example, Siri, Next-Word-Prediction, and other messaging apps include auto-complete features that attempt to finish users’ words or sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/about/</guid>
      <description>This is the about page for the test website. More info coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
