<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Federated Learning on Quantum Federated Learning Blog</title>
    <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/tags/federated-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Federated Learning on Quantum Federated Learning Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/tags/federated-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Pass: &#39;&#39;TensorFlow Quantum&#39;&#39; Paper</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post8/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 15, 2021)
In my last post, I summarized &amp;ldquo;How to Read a Paper&amp;rdquo;1 with the Three-Pass method. Now, I would like to apply this algorithm to one paper especially significant to my research: “TensorFlow Quantum: A Software Framework for Quantum Machine Learning.”2. In this post, I perform the first pass. This paper is worth a second pass, since it is directly relevant to my research.
 Review of First Pass (from previous post) Without reading details or illustrations, get a general understanding of the paper&amp;rsquo;s topic and how it will approach the topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review: &#39;&#39;Federated Learning: Why, What and How&#39;&#39;</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post6/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 9, 2021)
So far, the majority of my blog posts concentrate on aspects of Quantum Computing. Today I&amp;rsquo;d like to shift gears to the other side of my research: Federated Learning (FL). My goal is to glean a better intuitive understanding of the mathematical equations that represent the FL framework. I start with Saheed Tijani&amp;rsquo;s article &amp;ldquo;Federated Learning: Why, What and How&amp;rdquo; that was posted on LinkedIn on 14 April 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to My Research</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post1/</guid>
      <description>Federated Deep Learning on Quantum Computers Welcome to my blog about my undergraduage honors computer science research! I am excited to start working this summer in preparation for my senior year at William &amp;amp; Mary.
Brief Summary Many edge devices, such as cell phones, contribute to and require feedback from a shared deep learning algorithm hosted on a server. For example, Siri, Next-Word-Prediction, and other messaging apps include auto-complete features that attempt to finish users’ words or sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
