<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Classical Computing on Quantum Federated Learning Blog</title>
    <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/tags/classical-computing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Classical Computing on Quantum Federated Learning Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/tags/classical-computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Pass: &#39;&#39;TensorFlow Quantum&#39;&#39; Paper</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post8/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 15, 2021)
In my last post, I summarized &amp;ldquo;How to Read a Paper&amp;rdquo;1 with the Three-Pass method. Now, I would like to apply this algorithm to one paper especially significant to my research: “TensorFlow Quantum: A Software Framework for Quantum Machine Learning.”2. In this post, I perform the first pass. This paper is worth a second pass, since it is directly relevant to my research.
 Review of First Pass (from previous post) Without reading details or illustrations, get a general understanding of the paper&amp;rsquo;s topic and how it will approach the topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classical versus Quantum Computing</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 3, 2021)
There exist a plethora of methods of computation. The most commonly used computation is classical computation. Here, we explore the basic differences between classical and quantum.
Classical Computing Also known as binary computing, classical computing is a system of computation that uses bits (represented by 0 and 1) to logically store and manipulate information. Historically, all computers from Babbage&amp;rsquo;s theoretical &amp;ldquo;analytical machine&amp;rdquo; to the supercomputers produced by Hewlett Packard Enterprise&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary, Cray Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
