<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Quantum Federated Learning Blog</title>
    <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Quantum Federated Learning Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overview of TensorFlowQuantum Building Blocks</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post10/</guid>
      <description>This post explores Part II, &amp;ldquo;Software Archtecture &amp;amp; Building Blocks,&amp;rdquo; of the paper &amp;ldquo;TensorFlow Quantum: A Software Framework for Quantum Machine Learning&amp;rdquo; paper.
What is TensorFlow Quantum? In the world, there exists two Google software products belonging to two separate communities:
  Cirq, used by the quantum computing world, is a tool to build quantum circuits     TensorFlow, used by the machine learning world, is a tool to build machine learning algorithms   The TensorFlow Quantum library bridges these communities into a hybrid world, quantum machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matrices Behind Quantum Logic Gates</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post9/</guid>
      <description>The following post is a simple introduction to how quantum gates relate to matrices.
A Quantum Neural Network: Quantum neural networks are made up of layers nodes connected by edges. Here, we imagine each node as a quantum gate which receives an input matrix and passes an output matrix to the next layer of gates. Mathematically, these gates are unitaries, matrices with special properties (where the conjugate transpose is equivalent to the matrix inverse1).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Pass: &#39;&#39;TensorFlow Quantum&#39;&#39; Paper</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post8/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 15, 2021)
In my last post, I summarized &amp;ldquo;How to Read a Paper&amp;rdquo;1 with the Three-Pass method. Now, I would like to apply this algorithm to one paper especially significant to my research: “TensorFlow Quantum: A Software Framework for Quantum Machine Learning.”2. In this post, I perform the first pass. This paper is worth a second pass, since it is directly relevant to my research.
 Review of First Pass (from previous post) Without reading details or illustrations, get a general understanding of the paper&amp;rsquo;s topic and how it will approach the topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review: &#39;&#39;How to Read a Paper&#39;&#39;</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post7/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 10, 2021)
Over the course of this summer, I intend to read many papers related to quantum computing and federated learning. So far, most of my blog posts have been about articles and tutorials published online. However in the next few days, I hope to share a few posts about peer-reviewed papers. These are generally more complicated to read through and understand, and they are hard to write about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review: &#39;&#39;Federated Learning: Why, What and How&#39;&#39;</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post6/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 9, 2021)
So far, the majority of my blog posts concentrate on aspects of Quantum Computing. Today I&amp;rsquo;d like to shift gears to the other side of my research: Federated Learning (FL). My goal is to glean a better intuitive understanding of the mathematical equations that represent the FL framework. I start with Saheed Tijani&amp;rsquo;s article &amp;ldquo;Federated Learning: Why, What and How&amp;rdquo; that was posted on LinkedIn on 14 April 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review: &#39;&#39;Explainer: What is a Quantum Computer?&#39;&#39;</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post5/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 8, 2021)
On 29 January 2019, the MIT Technology Review published an article1 by Martin Giles on the subject of Quantum Computing. This piece, titled &amp;ldquo;Explainer: What is a Quantum Computer&amp;rdquo; is a short overview of what makes quantum computing unique and how it contributes to the technological world. In particular, this article stands out to me because of its easy-to-comprehend definitions of quantum properties. Here, I outline these properties:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Mathematical Theory Behind TensorFlow Quantum for Hybrid Learning (draft)</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post4/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 8, 2021)
Please note, this draft is a work in progress. For the next few days, I will continue to write here about the equations as I better understand them. Once finalized, I will update the publication date.
The paper &amp;ldquo;TensorFlow Quantum: A Software Framework for Quantum Machine Learning&amp;rdquo; by Michael Broughton, et al. introdues the TensorFlow Quantum library with respect to implementing hybrid models that handle classical or quantum data 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review: &#39;&#39;How to get started in quantum computing&#39;&#39; </title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post3/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 3, 2021)
Summary David Matthews&#39; paper &amp;ldquo;How to get started in quantum computing,&amp;rdquo; by Nature News, is an excellent survey paper of today&amp;rsquo;s state of computing. Published online just a few months ago on 4 March 2021, it summarizes fundamental ideas behind quantum computing motivating new research. The paper names leading companies and institutions who have been contributing to the swiftly growing field, and it distinguishes a few broad aspects of their approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classical versus Quantum Computing</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>(Last updated: June 3, 2021)
There exist a plethora of methods of computation. The most commonly used computation is classical computation. Here, we explore the basic differences between classical and quantum.
Classical Computing Also known as binary computing, classical computing is a system of computation that uses bits (represented by 0 and 1) to logically store and manipulate information. Historically, all computers from Babbage&amp;rsquo;s theoretical &amp;ldquo;analytical machine&amp;rdquo; to the supercomputers produced by Hewlett Packard Enterprise&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary, Cray Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to My Research</title>
      <link>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adbrei.github.io/qfl-research/posts/post1/</guid>
      <description>Federated Deep Learning on Quantum Computers Welcome to my blog about my undergraduage honors computer science research! I am excited to start working this summer in preparation for my senior year at William &amp;amp; Mary.
Brief Summary Many edge devices, such as cell phones, contribute to and require feedback from a shared deep learning algorithm hosted on a server. For example, Siri, Next-Word-Prediction, and other messaging apps include auto-complete features that attempt to finish users’ words or sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
